American Philosophical Society Archives. Record Group IIf. 1866-1886 APS.Archives.IIf APS.Archives.IIf
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Dec. 24, 1886; 10x8; Philadelphia. Post office
    Phila., L.S.:W[illia]m F.Harrity,postmaster. 1p. Enc.wanting. Concerning Phillips' complaint of treatment of letter.
  - Letter to H[enry] Phillips, Dec. 27, 1886; 8x5; Seidensticker, Oswald, 1825-1894
    Phila., A.L.S. 1p. Resignation from the Council.
  - Letter to [Frederick] Fraley, Dec. 29, 1886; 8x5; Leidy, Joseph, 1823-1891
    [Phila.], A.L.S. 1p. Agrees to prepare obituary of Isaac Lea. Enclosed originally in letter from F. Fraley to H.Phillips, Dec.30, 1886.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Dec. 29, 1886; 8x5; Mallet, John William
    University of Virginia, A.L.S. 1p. Enc.wanting. Sends subscription fee.
  - Letter to Henry Phillips, Dec. 30, 1886; 8x5; Fraley, F. (Frederick), 1804-1901
    [Phila.], A.L.S. 1p. Enc. Sends J. Leidy's letter in which he agrees to prepare obituary of Isaac Lea. For enclosure, see letter from J. Leidy to F. Fraley, Dec.29, 1886.
  - Letter to sup[erintenden]t of Adams express co., Dec. 31, 1886; 3x5; American Philosophical Society
    Phila.; L.on postal card S.:Henry Phillips(in rubber stamp). 1p.,end.,and add.,and env. Asking him to deliver the other package.
  - Letter to Henry Philips [Henry Phillips], Dec. 31, 1886; 9x6; Hensel, Bruckmann & Lorbacher
    New York, L. 1p.and add.,end. Concerning the two packages at the Adams express co.
  - Letter to Aristides Brezina, Wien, 1886; 10x8; American Philosophical Society
    Phila., T.Dr.of L.S.:Henry Phillips, secretary. 1p.and end. Asking for articles from him for the Proceedings.
  - Note to Henry Phillips, [1886?]; 5x5; Frazer, Persifor, 1844-1909
    A.N.S. 1p. Concerning W.Barker and T.Parvin.
  - Note to Henry Phillips, [1886?]; 2x3-1/2; Morison, Ella M.
    Thursday, A.N.on calling card S.with initials. 1p and add. She is too sick to come down to the library.
  - Memorandum, [1886]; 10x8; American Philosophical Society
    D. 1p. F.A.Genth, C.A.Oliver and J.W.Holland are mentioned,among others.